This love in my heart,
it will burn on forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
No matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting bones,
we'll reach it, we are home.
I'm
so truly grateful.
I ran into you on that day so long ago.
We laughed every moment
with tears in our eyes.
Till we knew we weren't alone.
The blowing wind came in
and joined us on our way.
And with it I know we'll rise.
We'll be flying up high.
Why, tell me why are you giving up?
Why, tell me why you want to fight alone?
Hey, what kind of future
do you think you have?
Your dream is already in your hands.
This love in my heart,
it will burn off forever.
Granting me courage, I
hope it will never stop.
I don't matter where you
are, nothing is too far.
With our everlasting
plans, we'll reach it.
We are home from the horizon
out on the edge of the world.
If there is a place that
I'd want to take you to.
Let's head for it then.
But as for the way we already know.
We promised it long ago.
You scream by your voice.
That can't break through the silence.
Feeling defeated.
It crushes your helpless heart.
I've got your back, I swear.
I'll always be here.
Let's put our fate within
this light under the sun.
Can you close your eyes and
just listen to my voice?
Let's find the answer together I'm
telling you in our path I trust that it
will lead us To another sea untarded
Cause now we are home On the horizon,
out on the edge of the world
There is a place that I want
to take you to Let's head
forward then But as for the way,
we already know
We promised it long ago
Hmm, Mama,
Mama What a cute little creature
you are You're all bones and
yet you're inexplicably alive
It's a miracle And my goodness,
you put up quite the impressive
fight back there why the Chess
Peacekeepers couldn't hold a
candle to your little jam session.
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma!
They don't call you Soul King for nothing.
Your power is like poison to them.
However, you're still no
match for these three.
With good reason, too.
I gave them life with my own soul.
So these guys are on another level.
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
Mama, we have completed the inspection.
We checked all his clothes
and didn't find a thing.
And the inside of his tube
here is empty as well.
Just the sword here.
Nothing hiding in his cloak.
Z-zilch Knight.
All clear.
He didn't take anything.
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma.
I am very delighted to
hear that, Soul King.
I'm so sorry to have
suspected you, my pet.
How frustrating.
This is humiliating.
I have this little pet peeve, you see.
I can't have you going and
touching my Tomate box or
snooping around making copies
of my Poneglyph either.
I would be a certified fool to carelessly
allow another person to
make it to Laugh Tale.
Ha, ha, ha.
My, my, my, my.
I'm not going to screw it up like
I did with Roger, believe you, me.
He used that strange
power of his to hear the
voice of all things and
interpret the stone.
But fortunately for us, we have someone
who will eventually have a similar ability.
The pirates who reach
Laugh Tale next will be us.
don't you dare forget that mama
hmm oh my sweet pudding speak
of the devil you need something
did your third eye open it's only
a matter of time my dear mama
come on is that all you ever want
to talk about with me i'm just
a half-blood anyway there's no
guarantee that my power will ever
awaken i apologize your mama is
just a bit excited as all you
have that rare three-eyed people's
blood in your veins if those
special powers don't ever come to
fruition then you're just a
creepy looking weirdo Ha ha ha ha!
Ma ma ma ma.
P-P-Ponin has three eyes?
No.
It's a secret that we know each other.
Don't say a word.
It's that skeleton man.
I didn't expect him to be here.
Well, at least he got caught.
Excuse me, Mama.
I'm feeling shy and what's happening.
I'd like to speak to you
in your room, please.
Of course, sweetheart, anything.
He's getting back up!
Is he a father into his third form?
It's Count Iwatori!
How annoying.
I'd better finish this quick.
From Baron Tamako to Vikao Niyoko,
and now to Count Niwatori—each
time he gets cracked open.
He gets stronger.
These are his egg, egg
fruit powers in this form.
He'll be invincible, a
true knight among knights.
Once he hatches, he'll possess
power that you can only dream of.
Come on, guys—we gotta stop him!
Look, I'm not gonna wait.
gonna wait
Fine, I'll stop.
Now's my chance.
It's nice to have so many soldiers around.
Don't do it, you crazy bastard!
Get back!
Ugarra fell for the bait.
Don't do it!
Oh, my God.
Oh, what a close call.
Any later and you could
have been killed, Pedro.
That was so reckless.
Pedro, I didn't expect
that out of you, Tia.
Can you, Karoo, even imagine how I felt?
Hey, Pedro!
Think of how alarming it is to
be screamed at from a mirror.
But you, Tia, came up with
this great plan in the snap.
That's our Pedro. Great job. Where are we?
Is this some sort of mirror dimension?
Wouldn't be the first
surprise I've seen today.
What's cool is no one can
enter or leave without Barrel.
So we're all safe.
And that means we'll have an easy
escape route once we track down Sanji.
In the meantime, can you
fill us in on what happened?
That's what I heard
worried about Brooke, too.
Let's hope you got a copy of
that stone without much trouble
Everybody's in danger.
Let's hurry up.
All right, Karen.
Have you finished drawing
everyone's portrait yet?
Mm-hmm.
Ready to go, Cho-Bro.
Oh, really? Nice work.
Let's show the mirrors what you drew
and ask them to help us out again.
Magic mirror in the hall.
Tell us if these people pass by at all.
Who are they supposed to be?
I saw that girl with the long
hair run by here earlier.
The mirror just talked?
So does that mean Nami
has broken out then?
And is Luffy still with her?
I spotted her with Boss Jinbei. Huh?
She's with Jinbei?
What?
Sanchi!
Answer me!
Don't let him get through, fool!
Sanchi! Hey!
There's something I need to tell you!
Where are you?
It's important, can you hear me?
I can't see him!
That guy's way too fast to keep up with.
Where'd he go?
Maybe in here.
It's locked.
Let's try that way.
It's you.
You're Sanji's sister.
I am.
Why did you grab me?
I don't have time for this.
Well, you're looking
for Sanji, aren't you?
He was here just a few minutes ago.
For real?
You know where he is now?
I need to tell him that
Pudding tricked us.
She said she was going
to kill him tomorrow,
and I'm worried he might fall for a trap.
What happened to your leg? Are you okay?
Thanks for asking. I'll be fine.
He's already aware and
knows about Pudding.
He's known this whole time?
He only recently found out.
I tried to convince him to
abandon the wedding and run away,
but he was worried about
the East Blue hostages,
as well as putting your crew
in a dangerous situation.
Are the hostages Baratie guys?
Santi's friends are my friends.
So if they need any help, I'll go
there and fight for them any time.
Would you like something to eat?
I'm okay.
I'm staying right here and
I'm not moving an inch.
I'm going to keep waiting
for you to come back.
And if you leave me here,
I'll just starve to death!
You're my chef!
No one else can take your place!
I'm not eating another bite of
anything unless you cook it!
At least, I don't have
to worry so much now.
Sanji knows what pudding is up to.
I'm really happy to hear that.
If he's not being tricked by
her, then I've done all I can.
Okay, Sanji's sister.
Guess I'll be seeing you.
What?
That's the wrong way to Sanji.
It's how you get to the
rendezvous point, though.
I won't hesitate to relieve
this man of his head.
You'll be a sacrifice for
the family, understood?
As long as you don't run away, the
whole situation will tidy up nicely.
All right, Sanji.
At the wedding tomorrow,
the entire Vinsmoke
family will be eliminated.
Leave my sight, bunch
of low-class pirates.
Sorry, Luffy.
There's no turning back now.
Something hit my house!
What the hell was that?
It's the middle of the night.
What gives?
Are you okay, buddy?
That looks like it hurts.
You thought you could escape, didn't you?
Oh, damn it.
I've got to hurry up.
I'm staying right here and
I'm not moving an inch!
I told him I'd be waiting right there.
and I'll keep my word.
Block their path!
This is troubling.
I believe they're
attempting to surround us.
Wonderful.
What should we do?
Can you cover the rear, Nami?
You can count on me!
I'm sick of this!
Huh?
Can they all drive? No!
I'm glad you're pissing me off!
You're a clown child!
Hmm?
Ah! Chopper!
What was that?
Chopper, why are you here?
Ooh, Chopper!
Carrot?
Mommy, we came to help you, Tia.
I'm sorry, really, really sorry.
Hurry, more enemies are approaching fast.
Nami!
Come on, get inside the mirror!
This really stinks!
What's bothering you, Prometheus?
When Soul King cut me, the wound went
a lot deeper than I thought it did!
Gah!
And it's opening up again!
My, my, you're so pathetic!
In that case, I owe our little
friend a word of praise!
He's the first person who's ever
managed to put a scratch on one of you!
Mama, do you plan to keep
that skeleton here forever?
That skeleton?
Pudding, I'm appalled.
Is that really all I am to you?
Yes, certainly.
Dear Claus.
This is a one-of-a-kind work of art.
I can't hide him away in a book.
So instead, I think I'll
carry it around for a while.
Please, no.
By the way, my dear,
you've done well yourself.
I was surprised to find out the Straw Hats
made their way through the seducing woods.
But now they're safely sealed
inside a book in the prison library.
I know I went there to see them; it really
serves them right, serves them for right.
Are you going to kill them of
course once the weddings over?
I also took the liberty of sending
bar mates to everyone in germa.
They're all so Intoxicated, we could
slip anything under their noses.
Good, but you should know: raise
you was snooping around me earlier.
She's very perceptive.
I already took care of it, though.
What's that?
You didn't kill her, did you?
Don't be ridiculous, mama.
Sometimes, I feel like
you don't trust me at all.
No, I simply shot her in the
leg and erased her memory.
I must be misunderstanding somehow.
Pudding, all this time I
thought you were a nice girl.
Be careful, dear.
You're our precious
little bride, after all.
If she tries to get revenge,
there could be a disaster.
I appreciate your concern, Mama.
But, thanks to her, I got a
chance to practice using my gun.
Even the artificially
modified people of Germa
won't be able to survive a shot from this.
You are such a clever little girl.
Then again, you are my daughter.
Tomorrow, your gunfire will
set my genius plan into motion.
I can't wait.
Everyone's attention will
be on the big wedding kiss.
That's when Sanji, probably
with a foolish grin on his face,
will slowly lift the veil over your head.
And then, much to his shock and horror.
He will discover you have a third eye.
He expected a beautiful face.
But now he sees his bride for
the monster that she truly is.
He'll be paralyzed with shock.
And that's your window of opportunity.
Suddenly you'll take out your gun.
Aim right between those curly eyebrows.
and shoot!
What?
Somebody is going to kill Sanji?
All of the wedding guests will be stunned.
They won't move an inch.
Soon the people of Germa will cry out.
They'll turn around and try to run away.
But it'll be far too late.
A wall of gun barrels will
be pointed at the Vinsmokes,
who showed up completely unarmed.
And before they realize the danger,
the floor will be drenched in blood and
endless cacophony of gunshots fills the
wedding hall as their bodies are pelted
with bullets even after they're dead.
All six bin smokes will lie motionless
on the floor in a pool of crimson.
More gunshots will sound off in salute,
and that's when the real
celebration can begin.
We'll devour the wedding cake
and wash it down with some tea.
After they've been stripped of
that useless leader of theirs.
I can claim Germa for my own.
And their forces will be mine to command.
Poor Joe, bro, does it hurt? I'm fine.
Wow, this is so weird!
We're inside the mirror?
You should be ashamed taking
up with such a wretched crew.
Hello, Barrel.
This is treason, there's
no doubt about it.
I had heard that you tried
to abandon our operation,
but Mama brought out the
roulette and you got scared.
I owed a serious debt
to Mama for protecting
Fishman Island after
Whitebeard passed away.
So I believe that it was only right
for me to repay her actions in full.
But looking at that roulette wheel,
I could only see death and evil.
Huh? Roulette?
You Karoo were wise not to
spin it, first son of the sea.
Five years ago, my partner was
faced with spinning that wheel,
hoping that he might be
saved from Big Mom's wrath.
But instead, she stole away his life.
Believe me, it's designed in such a way
that whoever spins it is sure to die.
The game's wrecked!
That's so messed up!
What did you expect, you fools?
Mama rarely lets anyone
leave this place alive.
Whether it's a mere trespasser or a
traitorous pirate who was once in her service.
She welcomes those who come to her
and kills those who try to leave.
That's Mama's way.
We're wasting our time.
Let's get out of here.
We have to hurry up and find
Luffy, Sanji, and Brooke.
Hey, that's not fair!
You're drastically over the weight limit!
Yes,
we can confirm with
absolute certainty that
the groom is fast asleep in his quarters.
Make sure that he doesn't
go out until morning,
and keep constant watch to ensure
that no one else goes in either.
Right.
Huh?
Well, ain't that a thing?
I fell asleep!
And in the groom's bed, too!
That's funny.
I thought he would be back by now.
I guess he's got other stuff to do.
Oh, well.
Time to catch a few more Zs.
Let's see.
Peckums was with them until
they entered our territory.
We know that their objective
is to get Sanji back.
And that there were six of them.
when Pudding lured them
to the island here.
So King is with Mama, which
means that he's accounted for.
Hands off!
And Pedro blew himself up in
the third floor courtyard.
Is that right?
That's two down.
Then out of the four who
went into the seducing woods,
we can check off the
rabbit and the raccoon.
At noon, we received a
report from Big Sis Barrel,
telling us that she
had captured them both.
So then that takes care of
four out of the original six.
Which leaves these two.
They beat our big brother, Cracker,
and then managed to escape
from the seducing woods.
But I know, beyond a shadow of a doubt,
we can find them safe and
sound in the prison library.
So why are we hearing
rumors that they broke free?
All before I was
torturing them to find out
Lola's location just
like mama wanted me to.
They didn't know anything useful,
so I had to burn them to death.
I realized that I went a little too far.
But come on, monthor—can't you at least
trust the word of your own brother?
Of course, I trust you!
you
I can't admit my mistake. Never.
If Mama finds out, she'll take
the rest of my lifespan away.
I'll be done for.
And what about Sanji and the Vinsmokes?
We've confirmed that they're
all inside their rooms.
All right, everything's good.
All of the intruders have been captured,
and the preparations
for tomorrow's ceremony
are being made in the kitchen as we speak.
Now let's give our adorable
sister an incredible wedding day!
We'll make sure it all
goes off without a hitch.
Expand your coverage and
patrol until morning!
I can't take opera's word for it.
Hang on, did I cook
this stuff for pudding?
Man, what was I thinking?
I made all their favorites out of habit,
forget them—you have to!
I don't
have to worry
about Luffy and the others;
they'll get away on their own.
The evil army of Vinsmokes will die,
myself included—just the
way Big Mom planned it.
It's for the best.
If she
gets what she wants,
it'll put an end to this,
even if my life was short—at
least it was a fulfilling one!
Oh boy, food!
Hey,
wait a second—are you Sanji Vinsmoke?
My door said you were asleep in...
you were asleep in
I'm gonna keep waiting
for you to come back!
And if you leave me here,
I'll just starve to death!
Get your hands off.
You heard me.
That food's not for you!
There was a noise!
Over there!
How dare you!
Don't you run away from me!
What the hell am I doing?